{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145734559","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145734559"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145739076","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145739076"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145743976","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145743976"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145749500","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145749500"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145754018","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145754018"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145760038","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145760037"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145764795","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145764795"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145769670","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145769670"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145774863","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145774863"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145781480","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145781480"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145793816","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145793815"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145798657","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145798657"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" cabe7018-3d59-422c-932a-da6ce919d396"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145807970","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145807970"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aaee9208-c8a3-4894-8c3e-75d869728572"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145808452","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145808452"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aaee9208-c8a3-4894-8c3e-75d869728572"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145815454","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145815453"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aaee9208-c8a3-4894-8c3e-75d869728572"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145824755","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145824755"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aaee9208-c8a3-4894-8c3e-75d869728572"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145831830","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145831829"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aaee9208-c8a3-4894-8c3e-75d869728572"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145838567","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145838567"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aaee9208-c8a3-4894-8c3e-75d869728572"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145844689","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145844689"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aaee9208-c8a3-4894-8c3e-75d869728572"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145855228","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145855227"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145857212","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145857212"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145858823","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145858822"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145861410","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145861408"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145862987","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145862987"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145872637","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145872637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145874193","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145874193"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145876964","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145876963"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145878540","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145878540"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145882380","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145882380"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145883937","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145883937"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145886047","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145886047"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145887659","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145887658"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145890303","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145890303"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145891889","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145891888"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145894866","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145894866"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145895868","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145895868"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145896024","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145896024"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145908378","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145908378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145915615","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145915615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 35195803-c8d8-4a51-a5ce-25fbbad7e03a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145979570","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145979570"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f1f7778b-c194-4e40-a590-8653adc8af0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" upepo_hadithi-jua-mno-upepo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" upepo"," userResponse":" upepo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146008654","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146008653"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f1f7778b-c194-4e40-a590-8653adc8af0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" upepo_hadithi-jua-mno-upepo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146008760","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146008759"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f1f7778b-c194-4e40-a590-8653adc8af0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146017480","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146017480"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f1f7778b-c194-4e40-a590-8653adc8af0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Vayu ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146026371","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146026371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146028503","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146028502"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146030666","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146030665"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146033876","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146033876"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146036158","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146036158"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146038420","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146038420"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146041275","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146041274"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146043518","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146043518"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146045745","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146045744"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146048978","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146048977"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146051108","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146051108"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146053236","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146053236"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146056217","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146056217"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146058412","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146058410"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146060639","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146060639"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146063589","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146063589"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146065904","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146065904"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146068245","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146068245"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146071302","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146071301"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146073497","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146073496"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146075658","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146075657"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146078795","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146078794"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146080975","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146080975"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146083157","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146083157"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146086316","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146086316"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146088725","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146088725"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146091164","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146091164"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146094343","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146094342"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146096624","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146096624"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146098931","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146098931"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146101934","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146101933"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146104165","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146104164"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146106387","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146106386"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146109345","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146109343"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146111680","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146111680"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146114073","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146114073"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146117212","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146117212"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146119616","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146119616"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146122033","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146122033"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146124993","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146124993"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146127270","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146127269"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146129513","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146129513"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146132746","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146132745"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146135077","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146135077"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146137320","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146137320"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146140666","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146140665"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146143129","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146143129"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146145535","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146145535"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146148335","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146148335"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146150456","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146150455"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146152628","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146152625"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146155983","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146155983"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146158273","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146158273"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146160566","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146160565"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146163696","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146163695"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146165916","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146165916"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146168113","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146168113"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146171083","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146171083"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146173163","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146173163"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146175241","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146175241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146178283","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146178283"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146180464","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146180464"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146182658","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146182658"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146185787","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146185787"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146187951","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146187951"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146190095","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146190095"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146193279","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146193279"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146195544","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146195544"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146197806","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146197806"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146197882","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146197882"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146197998","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146197998"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" aa4dfc25-f27d-48af-a81a-1f9945eddf26"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146219278","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146219278"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" a3057885-f7a0-4f2d-b9bb-9e56d09adeff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-2-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146224829","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146224829"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" a3057885-f7a0-4f2d-b9bb-9e56d09adeff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-2-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146231346","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146231346"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" a3057885-f7a0-4f2d-b9bb-9e56d09adeff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-2-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146243470","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146243470"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_4-7-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146249561","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146249561"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-8-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146256187","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146256187"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_0-8-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146262055","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146262055"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146267599","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146267599"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146273611","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146273611"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-7-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146282355","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146282355"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_1-5-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146289604","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146289604"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-8-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146296676","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146296676"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146301990","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146301990"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_3-8-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146307756","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146307756"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-9-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146314303","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146314303"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" c824a38a-5fc7-4e52-bd1f-ed866a0b1385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-9-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146325612","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146325611"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 1a064880-8f86-46de-9e77-928a8959bcc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TWIGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146329508","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146329508"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 1a064880-8f86-46de-9e77-928a8959bcc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TWIGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146331123","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146331123"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 1a064880-8f86-46de-9e77-928a8959bcc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TEMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146335484","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146335484"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 1a064880-8f86-46de-9e77-928a8959bcc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TEMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146336444","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146336444"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 1a064880-8f86-46de-9e77-928a8959bcc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146337087","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146337087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 1a064880-8f86-46de-9e77-928a8959bcc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146342160","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146342159"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 1a064880-8f86-46de-9e77-928a8959bcc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146342263","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146342263"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 1a064880-8f86-46de-9e77-928a8959bcc6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146354906","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146354906"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146355916","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146355915"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146356106","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146356106"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146356756","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146356753"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146357345","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146357345"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146357838","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146357837"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146358260","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146358260"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146358713","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146358713"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146358896","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146358896"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146359489","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146359488"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146359969","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146359969"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINNE"," userResponse":" MINNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146362690","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146362689"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146363254","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146363253"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146363777","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146363777"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146363990","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146363990"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146364374","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146364374"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146365167","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146365167"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146367502","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146367501"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146367954","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146367954"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146368155","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146368154"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146368910","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146368910"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146369765","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146369765"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146370237","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146370237"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146370410","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146370409"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146371047","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146371046"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFU"," userResponse":" SAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146371164","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146371164"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146371699","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146371699"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146373073","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146373073"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146376342","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146376341"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146377205","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146377205"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146377439","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146377439"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146377922","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146377922"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146378086","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146378086"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146378630","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146378630"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146379384","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146379384"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITATU"," userResponse":" MITATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146380799","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146380799"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146381302","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146381302"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146382338","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146382338"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOTEZA"," userResponse":" KUPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146382940","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146382940"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWEZO"," userResponse":" UWEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146383125","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146383125"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146383789","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146383789"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146386477","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146386477"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146387072","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146387072"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146387874","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146387874"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146388536","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146388535"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146389008","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146389007"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146389926","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146389926"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TALANTA"," userResponse":" TALANTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146393159","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146393158"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146394005","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146394004"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITENDA"," userResponse":" ALITENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146394472","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146394471"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146395417","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146395417"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146396230","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146396230"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146396984","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146396984"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146397560","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146397554"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146397790","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146397790"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146398170","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146398170"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146398731","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146398730"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146399947","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146399947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146400660","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146400660"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146402639","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146402639"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146403411","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146403410"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFANO"," userResponse":" MFANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146404371","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146404371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146405021","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146405021"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKETI"," userResponse":" KUKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146405193","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146405192"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146405572","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146405571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146406220","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146406220"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZIMA"," userResponse":" WAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146406712","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146406711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146407540","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146407540"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJADILI"," userResponse":" KUJADILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146407981","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146407981"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146408616","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146408615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHIMU"," userResponse":" MUHIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146411466","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146411466"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146411665","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146411665"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146412249","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146412249"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146413093","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146413092"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146413720","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146413720"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146414455","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146414455"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146414846","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146414846"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146415030","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146415030"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146415414","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146415413"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146416166","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146416166"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146419087","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146419085"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" WALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146419963","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146419963"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146420704","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146420703"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146420941","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146420941"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146421641","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146421640"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146422112","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146422112"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146422758","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146422758"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146423453","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146423452"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146426032","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146426032"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146426808","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146426808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" ALIACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146427010","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146427009"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146427394","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146427394"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146427827","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146427826"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146428321","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146428321"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146431421","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146431421"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146432350","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146432350"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146433124","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146433124"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146433959","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146433959"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146434621","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146434621"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146436971","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146436970"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146437584","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146437583"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146438550","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146438549"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146439585","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146439584"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146440755","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146440755"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146442073","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146442072"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" UNAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146442435","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146442435"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146442974","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146442974"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146443499","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146443498"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146444428","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146444428"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146447567","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146447566"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146448830","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146448830"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146449647","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146449647"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAKUJA"," userResponse":" ZINAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146449941","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146449941"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146450734","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146450734"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146453565","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146453564"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZISIKIA"," userResponse":" NAZISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146454266","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146454266"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWANI"," userResponse":" KICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146454914","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146454914"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146455558","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146455558"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146456595","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146456594"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZIIMBA"," userResponse":" NAZIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146459927","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146459926"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146460969","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146460968"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146461880","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146461879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146462431","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146462431"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146463175","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146463175"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146464117","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146464116"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146465014","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146465013"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOHISI"," userResponse":" ALIPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146465557","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146465556"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146468133","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146468133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146469447","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146469446"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIKILIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMSIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146470414","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146470413"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146471387","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146471387"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146472661","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146472661"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIOUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146473381","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146473381"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146475948","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146475948"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146476807","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146476806"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146477879","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146477879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUATIA"," userResponse":" KUFUATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146478179","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146478178"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146478741","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146478740"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146479218","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146479218"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146480156","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146480155"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146483334","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146483333"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146483887","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146483887"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146484358","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146484357"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146484527","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146484527"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146485322","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146485321"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146486301","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146486300"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146487058","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146487057"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146487641","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146487641"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146488474","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146488473"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ANGEMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146491062","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146491062"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146492185","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146492184"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUBALI"," userResponse":" ANGEKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146492758","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146492758"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146493475","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146493474"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146493987","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146493986"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146494741","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146494740"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146497651","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146497651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146498345","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146498345"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146499079","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146499078"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146499433","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146499432"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146500226","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146500226"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" WALIPORUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146501040","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146501039"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146502194","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146502193"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146503002","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146503002"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146503559","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146503559"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146506335","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146506335"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146507042","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146507042"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146507663","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146507663"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146508461","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146508461"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146509164","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146509164"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146509348","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146509348"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146509787","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146509787"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146510305","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146510305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146513051","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146513051"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146513430","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146513429"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" SHIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146514243","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146514243"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146515071","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146515071"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146515841","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146515841"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146518426","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146518426"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146519246","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146519245"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146521816","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146521815"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146522665","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146522665"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146523264","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146523263"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146523951","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146523951"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146524111","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146524111"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146524471","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146524471"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146525289","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146525287"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146526101","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146526100"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146526506","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146526506"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146526590","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146526590"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 8ce9883e-f550-4de2-8c4c-774eed41bd04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146538469","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146538468"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146539471","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146539471"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146539655","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146539655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146540292","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146540292"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146540847","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146540846"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146541329","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146541329"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146541750","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146541749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146542202","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146542202"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146542384","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146542383"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146542979","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146542979"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146543467","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146543467"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINNE"," userResponse":" MINNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146546246","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146546245"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146546810","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146546810"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146547333","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146547333"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146547558","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146547557"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146547942","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146547942"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146548746","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146548746"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146551008","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146551008"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146551459","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146551459"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146551657","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146551657"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146552418","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146552418"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146553268","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146553268"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146553735","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146553735"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146553906","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146553906"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146554549","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146554548"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFU"," userResponse":" SAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146554665","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146554665"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146555203","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146555202"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146556576","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146556576"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146559734","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146559734"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146560603","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146560603"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146560843","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146560843"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146561333","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146561333"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146561497","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146561497"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146562052","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146562051"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146562819","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146562819"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITATU"," userResponse":" MITATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146564250","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146564250"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146564761","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146564760"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146565777","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146565776"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOTEZA"," userResponse":" KUPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146566373","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146566372"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWEZO"," userResponse":" UWEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146566552","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146566552"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146567215","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146567215"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146569804","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146569804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146570406","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146570405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146571208","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146571207"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146571864","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146571863"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146572335","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146572334"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146573248","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146573248"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TALANTA"," userResponse":" TALANTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146576484","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146576483"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146577334","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146577333"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITENDA"," userResponse":" ALITENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146577805","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146577804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146578749","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146578748"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146579575","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146579574"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146580330","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146580330"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146580880","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146580879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146581109","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146581109"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146581491","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146581490"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146582037","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146582037"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146583232","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146583231"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146583916","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146583916"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alitenda mambo mengi ambayo wavulana wengine wa umri wake hawakuweza kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146585894","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146585893"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146586655","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146586655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFANO"," userResponse":" MFANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146587623","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146587622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146588263","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146588262"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKETI"," userResponse":" KUKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146588429","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146588429"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146588817","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146588817"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146589456","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146589456"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZIMA"," userResponse":" WAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146589947","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146589947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146590779","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146590779"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJADILI"," userResponse":" KUJADILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146591233","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146591233"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146591865","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146591865"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo muhimu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHIMU"," userResponse":" MUHIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146594845","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146594844"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146595043","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146595043"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146595623","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146595622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146596471","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146596471"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146597099","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146597099"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146597838","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146597838"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146598231","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146598230"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146598410","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146598410"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146598790","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146598790"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146599546","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146599546"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wazazi wa Sakima walifanya kazi katika nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146602501","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146602501"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" WALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146603372","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146603371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146604104","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146604103"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146604342","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146604342"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146605039","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146605039"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146605513","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146605512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146606166","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146606166"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146606865","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146606864"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliondoka nyumbani asubuhi na mapema na kurudi jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146609431","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146609425"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146610208","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146610208"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" ALIACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146610408","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146610408"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146610787","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146610787"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146611224","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146611223"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146611723","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146611722"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliachwa na dada yake mdogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146614790","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146614789"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146615721","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146615721"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146616485","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146616485"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146617309","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146617308"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146617964","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146617964"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kuimba sana nyimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146620351","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146620351"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146620956","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146620955"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146621899","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146621899"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146622938","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146622937"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146624107","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146624107"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146625432","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146625431"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" UNAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146625792","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146625791"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146626338","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146626338"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146626862","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146626862"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146627775","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146627774"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamake alimuuliza Sakima unajifunza nyimbo hizi kutoka wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146630871","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146630870"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146632148","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146632147"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146632963","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146632963"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAKUJA"," userResponse":" ZINAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146633256","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146633256"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146634046","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146634046"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijibu Zinakuja tu mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146636940","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146636939"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZISIKIA"," userResponse":" NAZISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146637640","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146637640"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWANI"," userResponse":" KICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146638280","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146638279"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146638934","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146638933"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146639965","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146639965"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nazisikia kichwani mwangu kisha naziimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZIIMBA"," userResponse":" NAZIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146643258","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146643258"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146644291","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146644291"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146645211","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146645211"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146645751","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146645750"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146646491","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146646491"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146647431","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146647430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146648321","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146648321"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOHISI"," userResponse":" ALIPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146648864","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146648863"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipenda kumwimbia dadake mdogo hasa alipohisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146651465","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146651465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKE"," userResponse":" DADAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146652776","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146652776"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIKILIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMSIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146653747","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146653746"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146654713","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146654713"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146655984","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146655984"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIOUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146656712","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146656712"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dadake alimsikiliza akiimba wimbo alioupenda zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146659215","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146659215"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146660074","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146660073"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146661152","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146661152"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFUATIA"," userResponse":" KUFUATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146661455","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146661455"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146662017","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146662016"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146662489","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146662489"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146663422","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146663421"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alicheza kufuatia ule wimbo wa kutuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146666622","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146666621"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146667172","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146667172"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146667644","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146667644"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146667808","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146667808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146668571","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146668571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146669536","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146669536"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146670280","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146670280"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146670855","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146670855"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146671678","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146671678"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaweza kuimba tena na tena Sakima dada yake angemwomba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ANGEMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146674286","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146674286"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146675416","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146675416"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUBALI"," userResponse":" ANGEKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146675986","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146675985"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146676700","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146676700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146677211","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146677211"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146677955","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146677955"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima angekubali na kuimba mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146680813","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146680813"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146681517","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146681516"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146682251","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146682250"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146682606","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146682606"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146683413","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146683411"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" WALIPORUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146684235","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146684234"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146685391","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146685390"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146686204","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146686203"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146686762","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146686761"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jioni moja wazazi wake waliporudi nyumbani walikuwa kimya sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146689457","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146689457"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146690161","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146690161"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146690770","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146690770"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146691577","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146691577"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146692273","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146692273"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146692460","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146692460"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146692902","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146692902"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146693416","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146693416"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alijua kwamba lazima kulikuwa na jambo mbaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146696149","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146696149"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146696522","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146696522"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" SHIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146697345","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146697345"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146698169","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146698169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146698946","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146698946"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna shida gani mama baba?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146701535","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146701534"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146702347","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146702347"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146704946","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146704946"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146705810","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146705809"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146706411","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146706410"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146707096","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146707095"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146707250","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146707250"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146707602","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146707602"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146708416","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146708416"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146709230","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146709230"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146710095","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146710095"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aligundua kwamba mwana wa yule tajiri alikuwa amepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" AMEPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146712634","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146712633"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146713286","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146713285"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146713797","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146713797"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146715190","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146715190"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146715766","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146715766"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146716395","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146716395"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146716781","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146716780"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146717650","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146717650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPWEKE"," userResponse":" UPWEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146718474","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146718474"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alikuwa amehuzunika na kuwa na upweke mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146721659","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146721658"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146722844","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146722843"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146725358","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146725356"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146726335","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146726335"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ATAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146726956","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146726955"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146727833","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146727833"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146728668","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146728667"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146729189","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146729189"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146729670","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146729670"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda atafurahi tena Sakima aliwaambia wazazi wake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146732513","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146732512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146733046","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146733046"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146733569","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146733569"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146734711","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146734711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIDHARAU"," userResponse":" WALIDHARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146735264","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146735264"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" WAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146735732","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146735731"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wazazi wake walidharau wazo lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146738243","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146738243"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146738461","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146738461"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146739655","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146739655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146741984","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146741984"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146742167","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146742167"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146742881","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146742881"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146743954","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146743954"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYEONA"," userResponse":" ASIYEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146746782","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146746781"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNADHANI"," userResponse":" UNADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146747196","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146747196"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146747538","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146747538"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146748568","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146748568"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani wimbo wako utamsaidia?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAMSAIDIA"," userResponse":" UTAMSAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146751569","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146751569"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146752222","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146752222"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146752951","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146752951"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146753767","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146753766"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUKATA"," userResponse":" HAKUKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146754324","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146754324"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo Sakima hakukata tamaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146756448","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146756448"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146756837","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146756836"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146757252","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146757251"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146757773","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146757772"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146758163","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146758162"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146758643","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146758643"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146759649","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146759649"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146760234","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146760234"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na dada yake mdogo vile vile alimpa moyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOYO"," userResponse":" MOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146762911","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146762911"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146763917","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146763914"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146764077","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146764076"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146764897","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146764896"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146766136","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146766136"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNITULIZA"," userResponse":" HUNITULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146766578","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146766577"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146767103","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146767103"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146767305","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146767304"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146767843","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146767843"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema Nyimbo za Sakima hunituliza mimi nikiwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146771213","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146771213"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZITAMTULIZA"," userResponse":" ZITAMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146772182","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146772181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146772419","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146772419"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146772663","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146772662"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Zitamtuliza tajiri vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146776048","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146776048"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146777119","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146777119"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146778057","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146778057"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146779048","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146779047"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146779451","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146779451"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146780014","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146780014"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146781489","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146781489"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMWELEKEZE"," userResponse":" AMWELEKEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146782162","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146782161"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146782568","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146782568"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146782963","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146782962"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146783164","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146783163"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146783564","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146783564"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146784286","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146784286"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku iliyofuata Sakima alimuuliza dada yake amwelekeze hadi kwenye nyumba ya yule tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146787605","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146787604"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146788186","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146788185"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146788278","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146788278"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146788872","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146788872"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146789430","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146789430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146789942","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146789942"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146790568","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146790568"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146791173","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146791172"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146791643","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146791643"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146792253","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146792253"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146793322","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146793322"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisimama chini ya dirisha moja na kuanza kuimba wimbo wake alioupenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIOUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146795547","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146795547"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146796230","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146796230"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146797115","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146797115"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146797384","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146797383"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146797870","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146797870"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146798720","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146798719"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146799682","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146799681"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIANZA"," userResponse":" KILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146800728","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146800728"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146801423","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146801423"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146802085","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146802085"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pole pole kichwa cha yule tajiri kilianza kuonekana kwenye dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146805116","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146805115"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAFANYI"," userResponse":" WAFANYI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146805670","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146805669"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146806406","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146806405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146807423","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146807422"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146807970","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146807970"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146808585","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146808583"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146809545","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146809545"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIZOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIZOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146810373","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146810372"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wafanyi kazi wote waliacha kufanya kazi walizokuwa wakifanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146813789","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146813788"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISIKILIZA"," userResponse":" WALISIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146814413","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146814413"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146815455","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146815455"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTAMU"," userResponse":" MTAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146815604","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146815604"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146816314","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146816314"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisikiliza wimbo mtamu wa Sakima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146818653","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146818653"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146819353","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146819352"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146820214","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146820213"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146820792","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146820791"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146821564","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146821563"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146822870","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146822870"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146823895","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146823894"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFAULU"," userResponse":" ALIYEFAULU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146824667","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146824666"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146825148","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146825148"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hivyo mwanamme mmoja alisema Hakuna aliyefaulu kumtuliza bwana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146827765","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146827764"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146828448","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146828447"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146828962","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146828961"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146829831","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146829830"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIYEONA"," userResponse":" ASIYEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146830709","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146830708"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAWEZA"," userResponse":" ATAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146831864","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146831864"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je huyu mvulana asiyeona ataweza kumtuliza?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTULIZA"," userResponse":" KUMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146835043","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146835043"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146836097","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146836097"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKAMILISHA"," userResponse":" ALIKAMILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146836645","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146836645"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146836991","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146836990"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146837548","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146837547"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146838652","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146838651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146839452","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146839451"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alikamilisha kuimba wimbo wake akaanza kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146842465","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146842465"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146842732","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146842731"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146843395","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146843395"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146844022","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146844022"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKA"," userResponse":" ALITOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146844380","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146844379"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146844850","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146844849"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146845473","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146845473"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146845632","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146845632"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146846251","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146846251"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146847868","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146847867"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146848679","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146848678"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146849371","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146849371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini yule tajiri alitoka nje kwa haraka na kusema Tafadhali imba tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146852347","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146852347"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146852588","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146852588"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146852980","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146852980"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146854149","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146854148"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146854680","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146854679"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146855442","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146855441"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUJA"," userResponse":" WALIKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146856017","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146856017"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" WAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146856873","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146856862"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEMBEBA"," userResponse":" WAMEMBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146857343","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146857343"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146858106","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146858105"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146858769","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146858769"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo watu wawili walikuja wakiwa wamembeba mtu kwenye machela."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHELA"," userResponse":" MACHELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146861401","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146861401"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMKUTA"," userResponse":" WALIMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146861884","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146861884"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146862058","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146862058"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146862761","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146862761"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146863374","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146863374"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146864828","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146864828"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMECHAPWA"," userResponse":" AMECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146865279","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146865278"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146865921","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146865920"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUACHWA"," userResponse":" KUACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146866379","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146866379"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146866587","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146866587"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146867169","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146867169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimkuta mwana wa tajiri akiwa amechapwa na kuachwa kando ya barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146870129","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146870128"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146870836","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146870835"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146872175","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146872175"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146872945","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146872944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146874252","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146874251"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146874616","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146874616"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANA"," userResponse":" MWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146875050","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146875049"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146875671","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146875670"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yule tajiri alifurahi sana alipomwona mwana wake tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146878840","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146878840"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMZAWADI"," userResponse":" ALIMZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146879797","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146879796"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146880219","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146880219"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146881207","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146881206"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimzawadi Sakima kwa kumliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLIWAZA"," userResponse":" KUMLIWAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146884478","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146884478"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146885474","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146885474"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146885732","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146885732"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146886352","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146886352"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146887358","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146887358"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146888071","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146888071"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146888667","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146888667"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146889371","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146889371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWEZE"," userResponse":" AWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146890448","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146890448"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAIDIWA"," userResponse":" KUSAIDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146891297","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146891296"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146891825","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146891824"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146894455","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146894454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146894562","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146894562"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146902014","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146902014"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146909317","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146909316"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146916395","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146916395"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146926901","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146926900"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146933655","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146933655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" e1120e7d-0ead-4c3a-884e-6b8ccb7ac4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliwapeleka mwanawe na Sakima hospitali ili Sakima aweze kusaidiwa kuona tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146942969","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146942969"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146944045","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146944044"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHESABU"," userResponse":" KUHESABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146944968","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146944968"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBA"," userResponse":" NAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146948308","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146948308"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146948812","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146948812"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146949459","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146949459"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146952441","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146952441"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146953241","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146953241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146953642","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146953641"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146954384","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146954383"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146957665","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146957664"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146958306","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146958306"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146958848","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146958847"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146961841","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146961840"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146961939","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146961938"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146969171","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146969171"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146978069","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146978069"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146989187","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146989187"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" 17a8c020-75fb-434a-80e7-128ea583cda0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146989262","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146989261"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" acef5a03-532c-410c-b62b-de9e8bd963f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550146997653","data":{"timestamp":" 1550146997652"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" acef5a03-532c-410c-b62b-de9e8bd963f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147004223","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147004222"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" acef5a03-532c-410c-b62b-de9e8bd963f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147010705","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147010705"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" acef5a03-532c-410c-b62b-de9e8bd963f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147016474","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147016474"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" acef5a03-532c-410c-b62b-de9e8bd963f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147021647","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147021647"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" acef5a03-532c-410c-b62b-de9e8bd963f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147248322","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147248322"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" acef5a03-532c-410c-b62b-de9e8bd963f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_46"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147248391","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147248391"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" b6447e56-5306-40b5-aca8-aabaac4d15f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAFI"," userResponse":" WASAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147254581","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147254580"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" b6447e56-5306-40b5-aca8-aabaac4d15f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_48"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye tulioga na kuwa wasafi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147270291","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147270291"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147272866","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147272866"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147274958","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147274958"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147275558","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147275558"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147276219","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147276219"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147280701","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147280701"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147287585","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147287585"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147294720","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147294720"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147302081","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147302080"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147308870","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147308870"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147317446","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147317446"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147325842","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147325842"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147333978","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147333978"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147342383","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147342382"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147343509","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147343509"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147348627","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147348627"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147350996","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147350996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147355743","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147355743"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147363040","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147363040"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147370834","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147370834"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147379524","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147379524"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147387776","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147387776"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147390558","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147390558"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147397895","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147397895"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147400181","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147400181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147402667","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147402667"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147413557","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147413557"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147426695","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147426694"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147435840","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147435840"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147445025","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147445025"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147451189","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147451189"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147459221","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147459220"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147465695","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147465695"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147470647","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147470647"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147480212","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147480212"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_150204"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}